<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<a3 project="SQL Source Control" author="Matt Turner">
    <plan>
        <root>
            <col title="left">
                <cell>DVCS migrations</cell>
                <cell>SoC licence sales increase</cell>
                <cell>delier soc with first class DVCS</cell>
                <cell>considered lots of ideas for new migs functionality</cell>
                <cell>support other DVCSen</cell>
            </col>
            <col title="middle">
                <cell>cross-branch mig scripts</cell>
                <cell>sessation of user requests</cell>
                <cell>deliver SoC and SCE with cross-branch migs stupport</cell>
                <cell>considered lots of ideas for new migs functionality</cell>
                <cell>support migs fro SQL azure</cell>
            </col>
            <col title="right">
                <cell>Support DM off-line deployments of dbs</cell>
                <cell>DM will be able to implement dynamic db deployments</cell>
                <cell>deliver a SoC that packages enough info in the migs folder to build a dep package without calling back to VCS</cell>
                <cell>not started; low priority</cell>
                <cell></cell>
            </col>
        </root>
    </plan>
    <checks>
        <item>Downloads are showing good increases, from 300 in May to 360 in June and 470 in July.</item>
    </checks>
    <issues>
        <issue>
            <name>On some days there are no developers working on SoC (when Jeff is HoSE)</name>
            <impact>H</impact>
            <action>New graduate developer to start with the team in September</action>
            <resolution>August</resolution>
            <owner>MT, AE</owner>
        </issue>
    </issues>
    <risks>
        <risk>
            <name>Reduced team size - developer work will become significant bottleneck</name>
            <likelihood>H</likelihood>
            <impact>H</impact>
            <action>New graduate developer to be recruited for the team in September</action>
            <resolution>September</resolution>
            <owner>MT, AE</owner>
        </risk>
    </risks>
    <improvements>
        <improvement>
            <name>Allocated area of the project whiteboard for team to add issues arising from the recent team changes</name>
            <status>DONE</status>
        </improvement>
        <improvement>
            <name>Compare Team providing stable engine build for SoC to use while they work on SQL2012</name>
            <status>DONE</status>
        </improvement>
        <improvement>
            <name>Team only taking stories of 5 Story Points of fewer into a sprint</name>
            <status>DONE</status>
        </improvement>
        <improvement>
            <name>In order to get all tests green, the team are performing Root Cause Analysis on one intermittenly failing test per day</name>
            <status>DOING</status>
        </improvement>
        <improvement>
            <name>The team is beginning to use ReviewBoard for async code reviews so they are better able to maintain flow</name>
            <status>DOING</status>
        </improvement>
    </improvements>
    <recognition>
        <item>TEST</item>
    </recognition>
    <summary>
        <item>Team has been focussing on our teamwork goal, working on the known/unknown feature.</item>
        <item>SoC v3.0.13 has been released, containing several performance improvements and a survey that's shown on uninstall.</item>
        <item>MT has taken over most of the Project Management responsibilities from CS.</item>
        <item>Team's capacity remains reduced in August with MT not doing development and the new developer yet to start.</item>
        <item>CVT is getting up to speed and doing some dev work as well as test.</item>
    </summary>
    <snapshot>
        <item>The team are still feeling the effects of changes in the SQL Tools division.</item>
        <item>Goals have not yet been re-aligned to the reduced team size.</item>
        <item>Team's ability to support sales and customers is also suffering.</item>
        <item>The next grad dev starting at Red Gate will be joining the team, but he will be the only one in the medium-term.</item>
    </snapshot>
    <escalations>
        <item>TEST</item>
    </escalations>
</a3>
